[Fate Chooses You]
[Episode 38]
Senior Bai.
If the heart is bound,
no matter how high your realm is
or how strong your power is,
you won't be happy.
If the heart is free,
everything is free,
even if your realm falls,
you have no immortal perception,
or you are a mortal.
If the Crazy Taoist's prophecy
is true
that among those born on September 9th,
there really is a savior,
then I believe that person
must be you.
S-S-Senior Bai.
Senior Bai.
Senior Bai!
Good riddance.
He deserved it!
Do you want to die too?
I want you to die alongside Senior Bai!
What happened?
Someone has activated
the Mountain-Guarding Formation
and isolated this place
from the outside world.
Without new vitality intake,
the divine Jianmu Tree
can't continue to grow.
I'll go.
Even with so little power,
you summoned me.
You feel bad,
and I feel bad too.
I've made a decision,
and I should let you know.
Have you really decided?
I have.
Then just do it.
From now on,
I won't be myself anymore.
And I won't have my memories.
I am just a piece of wood.
Because I gained your power,
I'm able to walk in this world.
To be able to see this beautiful world,
I am very content.
Thank you.
Whether you have your memories or not,
we will definitely meet again.
I hope
we will meet again in the future.
And then tell me
the things I've forgotten.
You finally came back.
I knew it.
No one
can resist supreme power.
Now,
what did you come for?
I need power.
Is that so?
That's not what you said
last time.
You said
you wanted to see the color of the sky,
taste delicious food,
sleep peacefully,
feel pain,
and like ordinary people,
go through the cycle of life and death,
living a peaceful and stable life.
Why?
Do you regret it?
Had enough of an ordinary life?
Then,
what do you want now?
Supreme power?
Highest status?
Or do you want,
like your ancestors,
to use absolute power
to reign above all living things
and become the master of this world?
I can help you with that.
No.
No?
I have gotten my wish
and lived an ordinary life.
I've seen
the blue sky
and the most beautiful colors
in the world.
I have tasted delicious food,
can sleep peacefully,
and have had happiness.
From now on,
how should I address you?
I can't call you Lord Lu
or Mr. Lu anymore.
So from now on,
I'll call you this.
Qianqiao.
Your cultivation was stagnant before,
so you wanted to
live in Wei County with me.
Now that you are
a Nascent Soul cultivator,
have you changed your mind?
No.
I still want to live
in Wei County with you.
When the time comes,
we will open a clinic.
You treat patients and save people,
and I'll help you
from the side.
Didn't you say that,
after finishing the fate
of Curse of Five Deficiencies,
you could drink the best wine
and have the most delicious food
in the biggest restaurant in the capital?
Although
it's not completely over yet,
today is your birthday.
So I prepared this on my own.
May you
be like flowers and leaves,
year after year,
sharing the spring breeze.
Forever cherish the joy
of spring with a smile,
and dwell in the world
as a timeless, longevity immortal.
I also have a lover, friends,
and family.
I almost live
the stable life of an ordinary person.
I am very satisfied.
The person I am now
wants to protect it all.
Protect?
I am in trouble.
I need great power
to protect all of this.
You have to understand.
To become a Perfect War Demon,
you have to sacrifice all your memories.
The good or the bad ones.
The tender or the painful ones.
You will become a completely new person.
You will no longer be you.
A person
is shaped
by past experiences.
Losing your memory
means the original you
has completely disappeared.
You will no longer love your beloved,
nor cherish all of this anymore.
Even if my memories are gone,
even if I am gone,
as long as this heart is here,
everything remains.
Like a dead pine tree,
no matter how many new shoots it grows,
it can never become a poplar tree.
I believe
a Perfect War Demon with power,
even without all memories,
will still do
the right thing.
You and your ancestors
are not the same.
I hope you succeed.
Thank you.
After my Ghost Covering Eyes was lifted,
I suddenly realized something.
What is it?
I realized
I like you even more.
If one day,
you are also hit by Ghost Covering Eyes,
will you forget me
completely
and not remember me at all?
How could that happen?
What if?
Sheng.
I am not her.
Void Stage.
Your realm improved
quite fast.
Yes.
Otherwise, how can I kill you
to avenge Sheng?
I am inside her body now.
Killing me
means killing her.
Aren't you two as close as sisters?
Can you bear to do it?
Come on.
Get out of her body.
Childish.
Get out of her body!
Junior Jiang!
Kill him!
Fighting with me,
yet you dare to be distracted?
What should we do?
You have the strength of the Void Stage,
but you can only
be beaten with your hands tied.
Aren't you doomed to die?
What's with that look?
You are Sheng's Senior Sister.
Logically, you should call me Aunt.
How can you be so disrespectful
when seeing an elder?
You don't deserve to be an elder.
Worse than beasts,
you bring ruin to your descendants.
She was originally very obedient.
I guess she must have picked up
bad habits from you.
How should I punish you?
Sheng.
This rebellious child.
You actually dared to resist me.
Do you think hiding in the spiritual sea
means I can't do anything to you?
Sheng.
Three to the left, 7 to the right;
9 upon the crown, 1 beneath the feet.
Two and 4 as shoulders, 6 and 8 as limbs.
Five abides in the central palace,
filling its core.
Enter meditation.
Sheng?
Senior!
[Sheng's Spiritual Sea]
Sheng?
Sheng.
Senior.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
He didn't die.
He turned into a blood crow,
hid inside me,
and controlled my body.
The one who attacked you earlier
was also him.
I know.
So what if you know?
I want your life!
Xin Mei.
Sheng.
Old cur,
die!
Great Completion Stage.
The thing Li Mofu works on
is not bad.
Using a cultivator's
immortal perception as a tonic
is such a great method.
Why didn't I think of this before?
Sheng,
you really are my good child.
I originally thought
that giving birth to a baby girl back then
was due to my powers failing.
Until I entered your body,
did I realize
that you are just like me,
both born with an innate spiritual body.
Good.
This is very good.
Crazy Taoist's calculation was right.
I indeed have an offspring
who can ascend to godhood.
And that person
is you.
It's a pity
that your immortal destiny
has been intercepted by me.
I will take over your body,
seek the great Dao,
and become an immortal.
I will live as long as the heavens
and shine like the sun.
An animal like you
wants to ascend to godhood?
In your dreams!
You don't understand.
Do you think all gods
are just and holy?
Don't be silly.
The only difference
between gods and humans
is simply
the level of their power.
Sheng,
actually, we are no different.
I am different!
I am different.
Sheng.
There's no use talking to him.
You are different.
I am different.
Right.
You are different.
Do you remember the poem
Master told us?
"All things must come to an end—
only when the sun sets
does the moon rise."
"As I descend the mountain path,
others will still rise to climb it."
Right.
Let's send him down!
Okay.
Sheng!
Senior,
get out!
Sheng!
Sheng.
Senior,
hurry.
Kill me.
I'm losing control of him.
If he gets out,
we'll all die!
Sheng.
No.
Senior, hurry!
No way.
Lord of Rust-Sword,
is your sword
just scrap iron for chopping vegetables?
Do it! Kill me!
I'm sorry.
Senior,
do it.
I can't hold on much longer.
Senior,
do it.
Do it. Do it.
Do it, Senior!
Sheng.
Sheng! Sheng!
Senior,
don't cry.
Sheng.
Don't cry.
What should we do?
How can I save you?
What can I do to save you?
Sheng,
I can't save you.
Sheng.
You should be happy for me.
I have avenged myself.
Xia Xuanzi is finally dead.
I have no regrets.
Sheng, don't say that.
Don't say that.
Senior.
I didn't believe in ghosts or gods before,
but after I met you,
I started to believe.
I always feel
that if there are truly gods
in this world,
they must be
just like you, Senior.
Sheng.
Don't sleep.
I will take you home.
Let's go back to Xin Xie Manor.
Let's go home,
okay?
Sheng.
Don't cry.
Don't cry, Senior.
Senior.
I really,
really can't bear to leave you.
I hope you will be happy.
Sheng.
♪ Hear the Gu curse
turn into cries for help ♪
♪ Blood-stained hand, sword drawn ♪
Sheng.
♪ Trapped in Qianyan Cave ♪
Sheng!
Sheng! Sheng!
♪ Even hell must be broken free from ♪
♪ With every stroke of hatred ♪
Sheng! Sheng!
♪ Let it grow into a dagger I wear ♪
♪ No need to show me mercy there ♪
♪ Let me take every blow ♪
♪ Drag my wounds through the hollow road ♪
♪ I'll pluck the passion
locked in my brow ♪
♪ At the end of the mountains,
I pick up fireflies now ♪
Sheng!
♪ Burn me down, I feel no pain ♪
No!
♪ I believe Heaven sees all ♪\
♪ Its wrath shines upon demons ♪
♪ But who will show me mercy? ♪
♪ I believe I'm innocent ♪
♪ Turned into dust and scattered away ♪
♪ I accept the blame of
numerous accusations ♪
♪ I offer no defense ♪
♪ To protect what I believe is worth it ♪
♪ I admit my heart
is as hard as iron and stone ♪
♪ Call me cold if you must ♪
♪ I'll risk it all ♪
Senior,
I don't want to ascend to the sky,
nor do I want to be an immortal.
I just want to stay in Xin Xie Manor.
Do you like Lu Qianqiao?
If you like him, then so be it.
I didn't like him before
because his power was too strong,
and I was afraid you'd get hurt.
Now he is just
a Foundation Establishment cultivator,
and he will continue to fall.
He can't beat me at all.
If he fails you,
I will kill him with my sword.
Senior.
Let's go back to Xin Xie Manor.
I want to go home.
The fish we raised in the pond last year
should be plump by now.
I want to eat your grilled fish.
Let's go back to Xin Xie Manor, okay?
You want to die too?
Death?
Why fear death?
In this battle,
haven't enough people died?
Master,
Junior,
fellow disciples,
and innocent people
all died because of your ambition.
You've harmed so many people.
Shouldn't the one who deserves death
the most be you?
Your master
was a Great Completion cultivator.
Even he couldn't beat me.
Can you?
Even if I can't, I must fight!
How could this happen?
Lord of Rust-Sword,
do you remember what your master
told you?
In your life,
you must travel 60,000 li,
raise your sword against enemies
99,000 times,
-and draw blood 36,000 times
-And draw blood 36,000 times
-before the rust fades
-Before the rust fades
-and the divine light reappears!
-And the divine light reappears!
I succeeded.
I succeeded!
Had I known you would
cause such a disaster,
I shouldn't have let you
leave Tianyuan Sect alive.
Can a person whose sword is broken
still fight?
A person with a broken sword can fight,
but a person with a broken heart
can hardly win.
Sect Master,
you want to become a god,
but do you know what a god is?
Hou Yi shot down 9 suns
to relieve the people from drought.
Kuafu perished,
but his body turned into the world
to bless all living beings.
They were humans.
They were fearless,
courageous,
and righteous,
honored as gods by the world.
But what about you?
You are selfish,
sinister, and ruthless.
You have no regard for the weak
and no care for the people.
With such a heart,
do you deserve to become a god?
Shut up!
Why are all of you
so annoying?
First Bai, and now you.
You always talk to me about
the so-called morality
of the common people.
Do you know
how ridiculous the path
you insist on is?
Do you really think
it's because the heavenly ladder
is severed
that you can't ascend to godhood?
Have you ever thought
that if the heavenly ladder
and deities were still here,
they would only strike you
with heavenly lightning,
burn you with heavenly fire,
completely destroy your soul,
and condemn you to eternal damnation?
Fine.
You had a chance to live,
yet you refused it.
Since you're so eager to die,
I'll grant your wish.
♪ With tear-filled eyes,
we face the desolate wilds ♪
♪ A thousand piles of withered bones ♪
♪ The lowly, in mortal flesh,
march first ♪
♪ All offered up in sacrifice ♪
♪ To build the stairway to the heavens ♪
♪ Forging an undying obsession ♪
♪ The blade is stained with blood,
and with countless tears ♪
♪ Sparks boil over,
and demons run rampant ♪
Lu Qianqiao.
♪ Heaven and earth
are destroyed together ♪
♪ Deeply knowing that the common people ♪
♪ Are an untouchable weakness ♪
♪ Do not turn back
to the pain of the past ♪
♪ Mindless killing must not be done ♪
Lu Qianqiao!
♪ With a clear conscience, a grand spirit
overpowers the majesty of heaven ♪
You are a god?
You've actually
become a Perfect War Demon.
What are you going to do?
I'm here to kill you.
♪ I ask the Nine Heavens:
what is the purpose of this life? ♪
♪ With my spine as my monument,
I shall never kneel ♪
♪ Though this life be wretched,
I will not sink so low ♪
♪ As to become a puppet of fate ♪
See?
This is the power of a god.
♪ Sparks boil over,
and demons run rampant ♪
Since you have
♪ Heaven and earth
are destroyed together ♪
become a Perfect War Demon,
you should rebuild the heavenly ladder
♪ Deeply knowing that the common people ♪
and reach the Heavenly Gate with me.
♪ Are an untouchable weakness ♪
The shame of the Perfect War Demon
has not been washed away.
And the curse of the Perfect War Demon
♪ Do not turn back
to the pain of the past ♪
has not been broken either.
You... you should go up to the heavens.
♪ Mindless killing must not be done ♪
Your future should be in the divine realm.
You shouldn't waste your life
in the mortal realm.
♪ With a clear conscience, a grand spirit
overpowers the majesty of heaven ♪
Are those your last words?
♪ I ask the Nine Heavens:
what is the purpose of this life? ♪
♪ With my spine as my monument,
I shall never kneel ♪
♪ Though this life be wretched,
I will not sink so low ♪
♪ As to become a puppet of fate ♪
♪ What is the purpose of life?
To draw my blade and slay evil ♪
♪ Even if I am turned to dust,
I will not regret ♪
Then die.
♪ By my will,
I shall bring back the sun and moon ♪
♪ And restore clear radiance
to the mortal realm ♪
♪ Rather than bowing my back
to apologize to the Heavens ♪
♪ I would sooner rewrite
this fated calamity ♪
♪ I demand the story
follow my own desire ♪
♪ To serve as its final conclusion ♪
♪ I ask the Nine Heavens:
what is the purpose of this life? ♪
♪ With my spine as my monument,
I shall never kneel ♪
♪ Though this life be wretched,
I will not sink so low ♪
♪ As to become a puppet of fate ♪
♪ What is the purpose of life?
To draw my blade and slay evil ♪
♪ Even if I am turned to dust,
I will not regret ♪
♪ By my will,
I shall bring back the sun and moon ♪
♪ And restore clear radiance
to the mortal realm ♪
♪ Rather than bowing my back
to apologize to the Heavens ♪
♪ I would sooner rewrite
this fated calamity ♪
♪ I demand the story
follow my own desire ♪
♪ To serve as its final conclusion ♪
So,
to become a Perfect War Demon,
one has to pay the price.
That's right.
A Perfect War Demon
needs to sacrifice all their memories.
From then on,
everything in the past
will vanish like smoke.
Those cherished
and precious people and things
will all be erased
and never be recalled again.
In other words,
a Perfect War Demon
is a completely new person,
a person
with no past.
♪ Honor and disgrace;
rumors and prejudice ♪
No.
♪ Everyone has their own take ♪
♪ Fingers coated in blood
and disasters brought about ♪
♪ Were never what I wanted ♪
Lu Qianqiao.
♪ The great way is fading away,
besieged by mysterious traps ♪
Lu Qianqiao!
♪ Who dares to treat life and death
as nothing? ♪
♪ In the blink of an eye, the body
collapses, and the soul is destroyed ♪
♪ The fire starts raging across the land ♪
Lu Qianqiao!
♪ What do you think is ♪
♪ The most impressive farewell
in the world? ♪
♪ The endless slaughter and massacres ♪
Lu Qianqiao!
♪ Do not wait until that thin snow
on the eaves ♪
♪ Turns a young man's hair white
before you regret it ♪
Lu Qianqiao!
♪ When do you think ♪
♪ The bloody strife will come to an end? ♪
♪ Burn myself to prove it
without looking back ♪
♪ Holding the morning glow in hand,
I paint the world ♪
Lu Qianqiao!
♪ The dawn light
illuminates the vast sky ♪
Lu Qianqiao!
Don't go!
I'm Xin Mei! Come back!
Lu Qianqiao!